Hand-holding is only allowed
under the following circumstances.
A, either party is in danger
of falling off a cliff, precipice or ledge.
B, either party is deserving of a hearty
handshake after winning a Nobel Prize.
C, moral support during flu shots."
- Seems a bit restrictive.
- Yeah, well, feel free to retain a lawyer.
Penny, I said, "Right hand, red."
Yeah, I heard you. I got red. Ahem.
(Amy:)Bernadette...
(Amy:)...left foot, yellow.
(Bernadette:)We should play limbo next.
No one beats me at limbo.
Penny? Amy? Bernadette?
(Amy:)That's my boyfriend.
(Amy:)It's open.
(Sheldon:)I got a splinter.
(Amy:)What do you want me to do about it?
(Sheldon:)Relationship Agreement
Section 4: Boo-boos and Ouchies.
(Sheldon:)You have to take care of it.
(Amy:)I should've gotten a lawyer.
(Bernadette:)Looks like it's just us playing.
(Bernadette:)Penny?
- Penny, we're out of wine.
- You should probably drive.